let Questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      ans: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which programming language is commonly used for web development?"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      ans: "Python",
      question: "Which language is known for its readability and simplicity?"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      ans: "Java",
      question: "Which programming language is used to develop Android applications?"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      ans: "Git",
      question: "What is the name of the version control system designed by Linus Torvalds?"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      ans: "HTML",
      question: "What markup language is used for structuring web pages?"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      ans: "SQL",
      question: "What language is used for managing and manipulating databases?"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      ans: "Ruby",
      question: "Which programming language is often associated with the Rails framework?"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      ans: "C++",
      question: "What programming language is an extension of the C language and is commonly used in game development?"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      ans: "API",
      question: "What does API stand for in programming?"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      ans: "CSS",
      question: "Which language is used for styling web pages?"
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      ans: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which language allows dynamic content to be added to HTML and interacts with the Document Object Model (DOM)?"
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      ans: "PHP",
      question: "What programming language is commonly used for server-side scripting?"
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      ans: "Assembly",
      question: "What is the low-level programming language used to write computer programs?"
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      ans: "JSON",
      question: "What format is commonly used to transmit data between a server and web application?"
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      ans: "Swift",
      question: "What programming language is used for developing iOS applications?"
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      ans: "Node.js",
      question: "Which JavaScript runtime is commonly used for building server-side applications?"
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      ans: "Bootstrap",
      question: "What front-end framework is developed by Twitter to build responsive and mobile-first websites?"
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      ans: "API",
      question: "What is the abbreviation for Application Programming Interface?"
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      ans: "MySQL",
      question: "Which open-source relational database management system is commonly used in web development?"
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      ans: "Ruby on Rails",
      question: "What web application framework is written in Ruby programming language?"
    },
    // Add more questions and answers if needed
  ];
  
export default Questions;  